Nikita Gaikwad

Assistant Technical Service Engineer

To associate with a total 2.2 Year experience as full stack Developer in organization that promises a creative career in progressive environment, Also provides an opportunity to enhance my knowledge and technical skills and be a part of team that excels in work towards the growth of organization.



8788593579



Pune, India

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Fujitsu Consulting India Pvt. Ltd

03/2022 - 12/2023

Fujitsu Consulting integrates the core expertise of the Fujitsu companies and its partners to deliver complete business solutions in the areas of IT Consulting, Managed Infrastructure Services, Application Services and

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Design, develop and maintain fully-fledged and functioning platforms with database or servers.
- Creating software solutions in line with business need and collaborate with internal teams to produce software design and architecture.
- Modifying the database structure, as necessary, from information given by application developers.
- Create new, dynamic, front-end, and back-end software products and apps that are dynamic and visually appealing.
- Understanding, Analyzing and Streamlining customer Requirements.
- Knowledge of software development best practices and design pattern.

Software Development DNG Technologies

09/2021 - 02/2022

DNG Technologies is a perfect solution for everyone who wants to establish a stunningly looking website with lots of useful functions.

- To Design, develop, modify, and debug software code according to functional, non functional and technical design specifications of a web application using java platform.
- To build the user interface or front end by using technologies like HTML,CSS, JavaScript and Angular JS.
- To design and develop the database by SQL Database.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer

Tatyasaheb Kore Institute Of Engineering & Technology

08/2018 - 09/2021

CGPA- 7.08

Diploma In Computer Science

Shivaji University Kolhapur

02/2016 - 07/2018 75%

SKILLS

C# Programming Language Dot Net Core **ASP.NET** ASP.NET MVC OOPS Concept Software Development **SQL** Database Angular JS JOuerv ADO NET Dependency Injection Agile methodology CI/CD Tool

PROJECTS:-

Rockwell USA (04/2022 - 08/2023)

- The Multi Banking System Interface is integrated to the future banking solution for the users who is having multiple back accounts in multiple banks. This interface integrates all existing banks and provides business solutions for both retail and corporate customers.
- Domain: Web Application
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Languages: C#, .NET Core, ASP .NET
- Backend: SQL Database
- Framework:- MVC Framework

U-Daikin-Oracle DBA Support (05/2022 - 12/2023)

- Provide DBA support with a high degree of customer service, technical expertise, and timeliness.
- Environment:Oracle
- Back-end: Oracle Database

Smart Health Consulting System (09/2021 - 02/2022)

- It enables users to get instant report on their health issue through an intelligent online health care Mobile Application.
- Domain: Mobile Application

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Cooking Drawing and art Tracking